Previously on Friends....
前情提要…
I tracked down Marcel. And get this:
我追查马赛追查到这个：
He's here in New York filming Outbreak 2: The Virus Takes Manhattan.
它正在纽约拍“危机总动员二 病毒肆虐曼哈顿”
Hey,buddy! Marcel!
兄弟，马赛…
Excuse me,this is a
抱歉，各位，这片场…
Closed set. We know. But we're friends with the monkey.
不对外，我们知道 我们是猴子的朋友
Good morning.
早安
Look who I brought!
伙计，你看我带谁来了
Your old friend,Harry Elafonte!
是你的老朋友耶，毛毛芳
Whoa,dude. Burn!
真惨！
I don't get it.
我不懂
He seemed so happy to see me yesterday.
它昨天好像很高兴看到我
Don't take it personal. He's under pressure,starring in a movie and all.
放在心上，它近来压力很大 你知道，主演一部电影
How big of a star is Marcel?
马赛现在到底有多大牌呀？
In human terms? I'd say...
用人来比啊，我说像…
... Cybill Shepherd.
…西碧雪佛
So you guys in the movie or you just really paranoid?
你们是有份演出的 还是你们小题大作而已？
Hey,Sal?
沙尔？
Jerry wants to know if the monkey's ready.
杰利想知道 猴子可以上地铁那一幕了吗？
Excuse me?
抱歉
Jerry is the director? Which one's he?
杰利是导演吗？他是哪一个？
-The one in the director's chair? -Gotcha.
就是坐在导演椅子那个 我懂了
Pheebs,walk with me.
菲比，我们走
Why am I walking with you?
我干嘛要跟你走？
We're just going over here so that we can get away from...
我们只是要走过来这里 远离那些…
...the horrible flesh-eating virus!
…嗜血肉的可怕病毒
For the love of God,woman, listen to me!
看在老天的份上，听我说
Is he looking? Is he looking?
他有没有在看？有没有在看？
The One With the Super Bowl,Part 2
-=BT之家DRM小组 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 河马压缩制作 本字幕为河马根据R3DVD OCR得来
六人行 第2季 第13集 超级杯后（第二集）
-We've got a problem. -Tell me.
我有个难题 告诉我啊
I can't do Chris' makeup.
我没有办法帮克丽化妆
She refuses to acknowledge her mustache.
她拒绝承认她的嘴巴上有胡子
-ls it bad? -lt looks like her eyebrow fell down.
很多吗？ 像道眉毛掉到嘴上似的
Unless we convince her to let me bleach it...
除非有人说服她 让我帮她漂白…
...Van Damme will be making out with Gabe Kaplan.
…不然尚克劳范达美 就得去跟大胡子亲热了
I'll talk to her.
我去跟她谈谈
I hate actors.
我讨厌演员
Nice camouflage. For a minute there, I almost didn't see you.
老兄，伪装得不错 我刚才差点没看到你
Excuse me.
抱歉
Is your name Chandler?
你叫钱德吗？
Yes,it is.
对，没错
Chandler Bing.
钱德宾
Do you know me or are you just really good at this game?
你认识我？ 还是你很会钓男人？
I'm Susie Moss.
我是莫苏西
Fourth grade? Glasses?
四年级呀，戴眼镜
I carried a box of animal crackers like a purse?
我常常像拿手提包一样 拿一包动物饼干
Susie Moss!
莫苏西
Right! Yeah! Wow!
对呀，是呀
You look....
你真是…
Great job growing up.
女大十八岁
It's nice to see you don't still wear the cap with the mirrors on it.
很高兴看到你不再戴那顶 缀满小镜子的牛仔帽
I graduated fourth grade and realized I wasn't a pimp.
升上五年级之后 我发现我不是个拉皮条的
Remember the class play?
记得班上的话剧吗？
You pulled up my skirt and the entire auditorium saw my underpants?
你掀我的裙子 全礼堂的人都看到我的内裤了
Yes. Back then,I used humor as a defense mechanism.
对，那个时候 我用我的幽默感来保护自己
Thank God I don't do that anymore.
谢天谢地，我现在不用那样了
-Oh,my God! -What? What?
天啊… 怎么了？
It's Jean-Claude Van Damme.
是尚克劳范达美
I didn't know he was in this movie. He is so hot!
我不知道他在这部电影里面 他好帅啊
You think?
真的吗？
The Muscles from Brussels? Wham-Bam-Van-Damme?
“比利时大汉”啊 “悍将范达美”
Did you see Time Cop?
你看过“时空特警”吗？
No. Was he any good in it?
没有啊，他演得很好吗？
Rachel,he totally changed time!
瑞秋，他完全改变了时空
So why don't you go talk to him?
那你过去跟他讲话嘛
Go tell him he's cute. What's the worst that could happen?
你过去告诉他，他很可爱 最糟能怎样呢？
He could hear me.
他会听到的
-I'm doing it for you. -Don't you dare! Don't!
少来了，好吧，我去帮你讲 瑞秋，不要…
Don't!
不要
Tell him I cook!
说我会做菜
Excuse me.
对不起
This is gonna sound kind of goofy...
这样会有一点怪怪的…
... but my friend over there...
…我那边那个朋友…
...who cooks,by the way....
…她很会做菜…
She thinks you're cute.
她觉得你很可爱
You don't think I'm cute?
你不这么觉得吗？
I don't know.
我不知道
Do you think you're cute?
你觉得你可爱吗？
We're getting off the track. I was supposed to tell you...
我们扯太远了 我是过来告诉你…
... my friend thinks you're cute.
…我朋友她觉得你很可爱
What should I tell her?
我该怎么告诉她呢？
You can tell her I think her friend is cute.
告诉她 我觉得她的朋友，很可爱
-Makeup! -That's me. I gotta go.
化妆 叫我了，我得走了
How many times must I touch you on the arm before you ask me on a date?
我得碰你老兄的手多少次 你才会开尊口约我出去呢？
Well,let's try one more.
我想再试一次
There you go. Ernie's,8:00?
我们去“厄尼”，八点钟
I'll be there.
我会到
And if things go well, maybe this time...
谁知道，一切顺利的话 或许这一次…
... I'll get to see your underwear.
…我能看到你的内裤
No one was around to hear that?
没人在这里听这个？
So what'd he say?
他怎么说？
What a jerk!
他真浑蛋
I kept talking about you, and he kept asking me out.
我一直在跟他谈你 可是他却一直想要约我
Naturally,you know,I said no.
我当然是说不行罗
Thanks,anyway.
还是谢了
He just kept asking...
但是他一直约我…
...and asking,asking,asking....
…约我…
If you want to go out with him,you can.
如果你想跟他约会的话就去啊
Sounds like a jerk to me,but
他听起来像是个浑蛋，但…
Jean-Claude,she said yes! I'll see you tonight!
尚克劳，她说好，今晚见
Thank you.
谢谢
Then Jean-Claude took me to Crossroads...
然后 尚克劳带我去“十字路口”…
...and we hung out with Drew Barrymore.
…我们在那里 跟茱儿芭莉摩鬼混
Oh,man. She's so smokin'!
老兄，她好惹火
She's got the greatest set of
她有对最炫的…
No guys around,huh?
这儿没男的？
-Does anybody need anything? -I'll have an espresso.
有谁需要什么吗？ 我来杯浓缩咖啡
I'll get it.
我还是自己去拿
If I ask you to,you'll end up drinking it yourself.
叫你去的话 说不定最后会被你喝掉
-That is so unfair. -I know.
好不公平啊 我知道
Like you'd drink her coffee after what you did to her with Van Damme?
你跟范达美那样对她之后 还要喝她的咖啡吗？
I have to cancel racquetball tonight.
乔伊，我要取消今晚的壁球
Marcel's trainer will let me have him for a couple of hours.
刚刚是马赛的训练师 他会把马赛让给我几个小时
You're blowing me off for a monkey?
你为了猴子失我的约？
We can reschedule for Saturday.
我们可以改星期六打呀
Unless you hook up with a bunch of pigeons.
对，除非你搭上一票鸽子
Stick a fork in me...
用叉子叉我…
... I am done!
…我熟了
Stick a fork what?
用叉子什么？
Like when you're cooking a steak.
像你煎牛排那样啊
I don't eat meat.
我不吃肉的
How do you know vegetables are done?
那你怎么知道菜熟了呢？
Well,you don't. You eat them and you can tell.
不知道啊 只要吃一口就知道了
Okay,then eat me,I'm done!
那吃我吧，我熟了
I've met the perfect woman.
我遇见完美的女人了
We're sitting on her couch, fooling around...
我们坐在沙发上 我们在亲热…
...and then she turns to me and says:
…突然她转过来对我说：
"Did you ever want to do it in an elevator?"
“你有想过在电梯里做吗？”
What did you say?
那你说什么？
I believe my exact words were....
我相信我的回答是…
How do you know if you wanna do that?
你怎么知道 要不要在电梯里做？
You just know.
你就是知道
We gotta go. Got a reservation in 30 minutes.
我们得走了 三十分钟后订了餐厅位置
What I had planned shouldn't take more than two,three minutes,tops.
我的计划最多绝对不会 超过两，三分钟的
Two hundred seconds of passion! We gotta go.
两百秒钟的激情，我们得走了
But...
但是…
... here's an idea.
…我有个主意
Have you ever worn women's underwear?
你有没有穿过女人的内衣呀？
Well,yes,actually...
这个事实上，有…
... but they were my Aunt Edna's.
…是我艾达姑妈的
And there were three of us in there.
一条裤子里挤了三个人
I was thinking it would be kind of sexy...
我在想，如果你今天…
...if you wore mine tonight at dinner.
…晚饭的时候穿我的内衣 会蛮性感的
You want me to wear your panties?
你要我穿你内裤？
Could you?
可以吗？
If I was wearing your underwear...
若我穿了你内裤的话，那么…
...then what would you be wearing?
…你要穿什么？
You're swell!
你太棒了
I made Marcel's favorite dish, banana cake...
我做了马赛最喜欢吃的菜 香蕉蛋糕…
...with mealworm.
…加了虫虫
Candle.
蜡烛啊
What do you think's gonna happen here tonight?
你以为今天晚上 这儿会发生什么事啊？
Hi,are you on your way over
你正要过来…
No,I understand. A monkey's gotta work.
不会…我了解 我是说，猴子得工作嘛
It's no big deal.
不，小事一桩嘛
It's not like I had anything special planned.
又不是说… 我计划了什么特别的
Rachel,why don't you start talking first?
瑞秋 那我们就由你先开始说好了
I feel that this is totally unjustified.
好吧，我觉得 她这样是完全没道理的
She gave me the green light, I did nothing
她说我可以的 我又没做什么…
Do you think I can't see you in the TV set?
你以为 我在电视上看不到你吗？
If there's something you'd like to share
好了，摩妮卡 你有什么话要说就说好了…
You had no right to date him!
你没有这个权利跟他出去
-That's the most ridiculous -You sold me out!
你这么说太荒唐了吧 你出卖我
-I did not! -You absolutely
我才没有出卖你呢 有，你有
Would you let me talk!
你让我讲好不好？
Did you just flick me?
你刚刚弹我的头？
Well,you wouldn't let me finish and I was
你不让我说完，我只是想…
That hurt!
好痛啊
Quit flicking!
别弹了
Stop flicking!
你，你别弹了
You flicked me first!
是你先弹的，是你先弹的
Let's not do this!
别这样，别这样嘛
Happy thoughts!
想点快乐的事！
Now I'm gonna kick some ass!
好吧，老娘要教训人了
All right. Now,I will let go if you both stop.
好吧 你们住手的话我就放手
You want me to stop seeing him?
你要我不再见他吗？
You want me to just tell him you're seeing him instead?
你要我打电话给他 告诉他你要替我跟他约会吗？
Is that what you want?
你想这样吗？
That's what you want?
你就是想这样？ 是的
-Fine! -Fine!
很好 很好
There we go.
好了
If we were in prison, you guys would be,like,my bitches.
我们要是在牢里的话 你们就会是我的女人
Thanks for letting me tag along.
谢谢你们今天晚上让我跟
Forget about it.
何需挂齿
How you doing there,squirmy?
你觉得怎么样，扭动先生？
I'm hanging in.
我窝在里面
And a little out.
有一点出来
So assistant to the director?
你是导演的助理？
That's an exciting job. You must have a ton of responsibilities
你的工作一定很有意思 你一定有很多很酷的责任…
I don't do the casting.
我跟选角完全无关
So what are you guys gonna eat?
你们大家想吃什么？
How come all I can think about is putting that ice in my mouth...
为什么我满脑子 都想着把那冰块放进嘴里…
...and licking you all over?
…然后舔遍你的全身？
Because I went to an all-boys high school,and God is making up for it?
因为我上的高中是男校 现在神要补偿我？
I want you right here...
我现在就要你…
... right now.
…在这里
Right now,right here?
现在？在这里？
Don't you think we're in kind of a public place?
你不认为这里是公共场所吗？
They do have the shrimp.
这里有活虾
Meet me in the bathroom.
到洗手间等我
I'm going to the bathroom now.
现在我要去洗手间了
Come on.
来呀
All right,mister.
好，先生
Let's see those panties.
给我看那条内裤
Alrighty.
遵命
But you know what would be even sexier?
你知道怎么样会更性感吗？
What?
怎么样？
If you didn't have your shirt tucked into them.
你没把你的衬衫塞进去的话
All right. Now,I would like to see you wearing nothing but them.
好，现在呢 我想看你只穿那件内裤
Take your clothes off.
把衣服脱下来
I hope you realize this means we'll miss hearing about the specials.
好吧，但是你要知道这表示 我们会错过特餐的介绍
Come on,hurry!
来，快点…
Do you want this done quick or done right?
你要我快点弄好 还是要我做得好？
All right,turn around. I wanna see you from behind.
好，转过去，我要看你的后面
Somebody's been doing his Buns of Steel video.
有人跟着 “钢铁玻璃”录影带运动
So you want me to clench anything or...?
所以你要我缩紧什么吗？ 或者是…
Susie?
苏西…
This is for the fourth grade.
这个就是报四年级的仇
-What do you mean? -What do I mean?
什么意思啊？ 什么“什么意思”？
What do I mean?!
什么意思？！
I mean underpants,mister! That's what I mean!
我的意思是内裤，先生 那就是我的意思
What? What do you mean?
什么意思？
My skirt...
我的裙子…
...you lifted. IKids laughing!
…你掀开了，大家笑了
I was Susie Underpants till I was 18!
到十八岁大家还叫我内裤苏西
That was in fourth grade! How could you still be upset?
那是四年级的事了 你怎会到现在都还在生气呢？
Call me in 20 years and tell me if you're still upset about this.
你二十年后打电话给我 告诉我你是不是还在生气
I hope you realize you're not getting these underpants back!
我也要告诉你 你这条内裤我是不会还你的
I can't believe this.
我真不敢相信
Just two weeks ago, I was watching Sudden Death...
两个礼拜前 我还在看“绝命杀阵”…
...and now I'm on a date with Jean-Claude Van Damme.
…现在我竟然在跟范达美约会
Can you beat up that guy?
你能打扁那个砘锫穑
-Can you beat up that guy? -Sure.
扁这个 当然
This is so wild.
这太疯狂了
I gotta admit,I was surprised that you agreed to go on a blind date.
我得承认我有点奇怪 你会同意跟我来个盲目约会
Normally,I would not do it.
通常我是不会答应的
What made you make the exception for me?
是吗？ 那你为什么会为我破例呢？
Rachel told me...
因为瑞秋告诉我说…
...you were dying to have a threesome with me and Drew Barrymore.
…你想跟我还有茱儿芭莉摩 来个“三人行”啊
By the way,Drew has some ground rules and....
对了，茱儿她有一些规矩的…
Say you're sorry!
说你对不起我
Say it!
说！
No! I'm not gonna!
不，我才不要跟你说抱歉呢
Say it! Say it! Great!
快说…好极了
Say you're sorry or your sweater gets it.
瑞秋，道歉 不然你的毛衣就遭殃
That is my favorite sweater! That is my third-date sweater!
那是我最喜欢的毛衣 我第三次约会的毛衣
Say you're sorry.
说，你很抱歉
You wanna play? Okay,let's play.
你想玩，是不是？
Let's play.
好，咱们就来玩
What'll you do?
你想怎么样？
Give me back my sweater or it's handbag marinara.
把毛衣还给我 不然我就酱腌皮包
You don't have the guts.
你才不敢这么做
Yeah? At least I wasn't too chicken to tell some guy he was cute.
是吗？至少我不会不敢 告诉男人，我觉得他很可爱
Stop! Stop the madness!
好了，住手，你们别疯了
This is crazy!
你们两个疯了
Who can remember why you're fighting in the first place?
现在你们谁还记得 你们本来在吵些什么东西吗？
Yes,that's right.
对，没错
But still....
但是…
Look at your purse!
看看你的皮包
Look at your sweater!
看看你的毛衣
Look at yourselves!
看看你们两个人
I'll help you fix your sweater.
我会帮你补毛衣的
I'll help you...
我会帮你…
...throw out your purse.
…丢掉皮包
I'm sorry I made you stop seeing him.
对不起，我阻止你再见他
I'm sorry I went out with him when I knew you liked him.
对不起 我知道你喜欢他还跟他约会
I'm sorry that I borrowed your gloves.
对不起，我…借了你的手套
Joey?
乔伊？
Ma?
妈？
What are you doing here? I thought you guys took off.
你在这儿干嘛？ 我以为你们走了
She took off with my clothes!
她带着我的衣服走了
-Are you naked in there? -Well,not exactly.
你一丝不挂 不完全是
I'm wearing panties.
我穿着女生内裤
You always wear panties?
你经常穿女生内裤吗？
No,no. This is the first time.
不…这是第一次
Talk about your bad luck!
你还真够倒霉
The first time you try panties and someone walks off with your clothes.
第一次试女生内裤 然后衣服就被别人给带走了
I was not trying them out. Susie asked me to wear them.
不是我要穿的 是苏西叫我穿的
Let me see!
让我看看 不要
No! I'm not letting you or anybody else see,ever!
我才不让你或任何人看呢
All right,all right!
好吧…
Someone's flossing!
有人在用“牙线”
Joey,some people don't like that.
乔伊，有些人不喜欢那样的
Chandler's wearing panties.
钱德穿女生内裤
What?
什么？
-Let me see! -You don't have to see!
让我看 不…你不要看
Hi,tushy!
小屁屁
One of you give me your underpants.
你们谁把你们的内裤借我穿
I'm not wearing any.
帮不上忙，我不穿内裤的
How can you not be wearing any?
你怎么会没穿内裤呢？
I'm getting heat from the guy in the hot pink thong.
穿粉红丁字裤的人 倒训起人来了
Look,Ross. I'll give you $50 for your underpants.
听我说，罗斯，我出五十块钱 买你的内裤，好吗？
中央公园
-Can I have the milk? -I'm almost done with it.
菲比，牛奶用完给我好吗？ 我快好了
Keep your panties on.
拉住裤裤不要急嘛
And I'm in the movie!
各位，我在电影里了
-What happened? -A virus victim called in sick...
怎么了？ 有个病者请病假…
...so Cathy recommended me and boom! I'm dying on a gurney!
…所以凯西就推荐我上场 我会死在担架上
Marcel just finished his last scene, if you wanna go say goodbye.
罗斯，马赛刚拍完最后一幕 如果你要去现场跟它道别就…
That's okay. He's probably got parties to go to and stuff.
不，没关系啦 他说不定还有派对什么的要去
He's moved on. That's the way it goes,right?
它继续它的生活了 生活就是这样子，对不对？
Oh,my God!
天啊
What?
什么？
Looks like we made it
看来我们成功了
Left each other on the way...
成功忘记对方…
... to another love
…找到新欢
Looks like we made it
看来我们成功了
Or I thought so,till today
今天以前，我还如是想
Until you were there,everywhere
直到看到你为止
And all I could taste was Love the way we made it
看到你，往日回忆涌上心头
Looks like we made it
看来我们成功了
I think I want to write a song about all this.
我想我应该写一首 关于这件事的歌
Except one of the strings on my guitar is broken.
只是我的吉他有条弦断了
Chandler,can I borrow your G-string?
钱德，丁字裤借我，好吗？
-How long you been waiting to say that? -About 20 minutes!
你等说这句话等了很久了吧？ 大概二十分钟啊
Can't you see what's going on here? This man is dying!
你们看不出来吗？ 这个人快死了
Cut!
停
Can't you see what's going on here? This man is dying!
你们看不出来吗？ 这个人快死了
Cut!
停
Can't you see what's going on here? This man is dying!
你们看不出来吗？ 这个人快死了
Mommy!
妈咪
Can't you see what's going on? This man is dead!
你们看不出来吗？ 这个人死了